{
    "subject": "resource/James_Blunt",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Musician",
    "human_readable": "James Blunt's occupation is Musician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9747666716575623,
            "question": "Is James Blunt a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8060100674629211,
            "question": "Has James Blunt collaborated with any other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7678273320198059,
            "question": "What genre of music does James Blunt perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7117226719856262,
            "question": "When did James Blunt start his music career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6596912741661072,
            "question": "What are some of James Blunt's famous songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6284358501434326,
            "question": "What is James Blunt known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5532716512680054,
            "question": "Has James Blunt won any awards for his music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49255743622779846,
            "question": "What instruments does James Blunt play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4469184875488281,
            "question": "Where is James Blunt from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28504231572151184,
            "question": "What does James Blunt do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Blunt's occupation is Musician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7905_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is James Blunt from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7905_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments does James Blunt play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7905_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has James Blunt won any awards for his music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7905_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7905_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that James Blunt is an English singer, songwriter, and musician. Therefore, the statement that his occupation is Musician is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}